AUSTIN FISK

Http://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~fisk/ | 608-393-5902 | fiskaustin.af@gmail.com

Education and Training

University of Wisconsin - Madison — Madison, WI, USA Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Graduated: May 2018

Overview

Proven Embedded Software Engineer with 4+ years of experience. I excel in bringing up hardware from Rev 1 to Release. My expertise is in Embedded C with branches out into many other areas of engineering such as PCB Design, 3D Design, and Automobile Data. My personal projects display a wide array of my engineering experience. These projects are available for viewing at https://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~fisk/. The 433Mhz Remote and Pool Monitoring Machine display the largest array of skills such as Embedded Firmware, Web Server, Circuit/PCB Design, and 3D Design.

Experience

Embedded Software Engineer

Aug 2022 to Current

HP Tuners — Buffalo Grove, IL

Embedded C and C++, Hardware bring up, PCB Design, I2C, SPI, CAN, Serial, Serial Over CAN, KLine, TX/RX for 315/433MHz as well as 125KHz signals, Bootloader for an App with OTA updates, persisting variables through low power and no power states, Bit Bang PIC Flash Programming (ICSP)

Embedded Software Engineer

Jan 2021 to Aug 2022

Reconyx — Verona, WI

Developed embedded C code for the system UI, built upon the iCatch V37 Image processor Persisting and loading user configuration settings

I2C communications between the House Keeper and the Image Processor chip as well as various other devices

Test Automation Developer

Jan 2019 to Current

MCANTA — Madison, WI

Working with customers and fellow employees to assist in their robotic process automation development. Copado and Eggplant platforms.

Skills

- Programming Languages: C, Python, Java, Visual Basic, Assembly, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, SenseTalk, PaceWords
- Optimization/Speed: Multi Thread on Embedded Systems, Bus Traffic Configuration, Power Saving, Interrupts, Measuring Speed with Ossilloscope
- Failure Evaluation: Photo Metadata, Firebase Queries

- User Interface Design: UI Mock Up, UI Design, Persisting Options
- Hardware Skills: Simple PCB Design,
 Oscilloscope, Logic Analyzer, Soldering
- Additional Trainings: Automotive Electrical 1, 2, & 3. Chip Whisperer. C++ Design Patterns. C++ advanced class. PCB Full Spectrum (Altium). Embedded System Security for C/C++ Developers.